[{"answer": "Look, I quit", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "With me you can always do business", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It isn't a question of knowing what to do, it's knowing how to get in one that counts", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Now listen, we've got a tip that the my friend family has finally made a deal with that chorus dame", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, little my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Well", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " Get going where? I can write that yarn without stepping out of the office", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Fine newspaper the that place", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I knew your managing editor very well", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "May I use your telephone", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You're all right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Now get this, my friend. My name is my friend. Always was my friend", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "That's so", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " And live on your salary, I suppose", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " What play", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, live on my salary", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "My play", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm not quitting", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I know that", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Darling, I don't care whether you can look my friend in the face or not, but you're gonna be a good boy and wear garters", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Who shall I say, madam", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes, miss", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, daughter of the slums", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Aw, you wanted to see some life in the raw, huh? Well gal, I'm afraid we ain't got no raw life up here", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What did you do to that hair? And where did you get that dress", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Oh, you dyed one and washed the other. Well! You certainly look good", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yes. As a matter of fact, you failed to mention that my friend was a girl", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Yes", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hello, there, my friend", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I want to see my friend. Oh excuse me", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "a beautiful pair of shoulders! But listen now, as a favor, will you please make it snappy, Laughing Waters, and tell my friend I gotta see him because if you don't my whole family's going to die", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well, I got a seat, but I have no place to put it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes, I said it. Sure, I said it. I didn't say it for publication, however", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yes, I'm sorry, I struck him right here in your house. And I'll strike anybody in anybody's house that calls me a Cinderella Man", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Pardon me, madam. They phoned through from the Mayor's committee to remind you it's past the hour for the reception", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "They've been ready for the last half hour", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes, I know, but they scare me to death. This is the fourth dinner you've taken me to this week. I'm running out of material", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes, there are always too many other people around", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " What am I going downstairs and tell those people", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " my friend, would you mind telling me why you're not going", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "No! Well, well, well! That's all right, if you like it. Can anybody do that", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Oh my. You mean, some people are born and never will become putterers", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "How about me?  Do you think if I concentrated and put my whole soul into it, that some day I might be a putterer", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Well, if I couldn't be a good putterer, I wouldn't want to putter. But why? What makes you think I couldn't be a good putterer", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Been where", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Never even been to that place", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Then how do you expect to write about it", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Did my friend draw on his imagination", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "I don't know a thing about him, but isn't he the one you're always yelling about", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Gee, that's an idea, my friend. That's an idea there. I wonder now..", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " And there's her mother", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Surely, sit down. If I had known you were coming, I would have thrown you up a waffle", "docId": "Platinum_Blonde.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You don't", "qsentId": 58}]